Our next viewer's question is from YouTube itself
and his name is Mahesh and Mahesh
wants to know the opinion on ICICI LBRD and Akshay, let me
tell you his buying price,
he has bought ICICI LBRD at the level of 340
and I would just say that at what great
levels his buying is.  You will see that the
profit is a huge profit.
Tell me, when there is such a huge profit
then we don't understand what opinion we should
give.  But still Akshay, tell me
how much should be invested in this bumper profit?
Yes, you have made a very good entry
and according to me, there is
no need for you to book profits from this
because technically I am looking at the long term picture
because this is your long term
investment holding.  So here we can get
clarity that 1700 is
a new support base
defined by ICICI LBRD on the long term charts.  However, in
my opinion, after a slight recovery for the last three-four months, the
stock
is confined within a range.  But the kind of
technical setup it is, it seems that if
held from a long term horizon, then the all time
high of around 2300 will be its first potential
target and after that if that
breakout is also seen then perhaps the
stock can touch 2500 or 2600.  So
for the long term horizon, this is definitely a
hold.  1700 This
is your new support base.  If you want to take the trail stop loss approach then
1650 will be your trail stop loss.
But hold for long term and
huge gains can be
made in the coming years from 2500 to 2600 potential targets.
This is my belief.
So, you are advised to stay tuned and there is every hope that
you will make even more bumper profits in the times to come.
So don't rush to run away from here.
[music]